[theme music]
Okay, Michelle, it's time
to go over to the big-girl wall
and see how much taller you are.
Yay!
'Okay, up against
the wall, young lady.'
Ooh, I'm very tall.
Alright, Michelle, arms down.
Now, stand up straight.
Okay, let's see.
Now you're..
...cheating.
No tippy toes?
No tippy toes.
Oh, nuts!
Okay, Michelle,
but look at this.
It's a good news.
Ah! You're
half an inch taller.
[cheering]
Big deal. See ya.
[Jesse Frederick singing
"Everywhere You Look"]
♪ Ah ah ah ah ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ Whatever happened
to predictability ♪
♪ The milk man the paper boy ♪
♪ Evening TV ♪
♪ When did I get
to living here ♪
♪ Somebody tell me please ♪
♪ This whole world's ♪
♪ Confusing me ♪
♪ Clouds as mean ♪
♪ As you've ever seen ♪
♪ And a bird ♪
♪ Who knows your tune ♪
♪ And that little voice ♪
♪ Inside you whispers ♪
♪ Kid don't sell ♪
♪ Your dreams so soon ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ There's a heart ♪
♪ A hand to hold on to ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ There's a face ♪
♪ Of somebody who needs you ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ When you're lost out there ♪
♪ And you're all alone ♪
♪ A light is waitin' ♪
♪ To carry you home ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ Chip-a-dee-ba-ba-dow ♪♪
[instrumental music]
Alright, bed time, Michelle.
You got a big day tomorrow.
It's your first day
of pre-school.
I'm not sleepy.
Oh, yes, you are.
Now, hop into bed.
Hop!
Hop.
Hop in to bed!
Hey, Michelle,
isn't this a pretty dress?
Oh, it's beautiful. I think
you need that and a husky.
Let's go to school now.
No, Michelle,
where are you going?
Pre-school doesn't start
until tomorrow morning.
If you go to school now,
you'll be the only one there.
You could come too.
I need a ride.
Why don't the four of
us mellow out Michelle
with a little bedtime
story about her
first day at pre-school?
- Great.
- Okay.
What?
Oh, no, no.
No, no, no.
I'm not the story guy.
I'm the dress guy. See.
I pick out dresses.
That's my specialty. That..
What am I bragging about?
I'm in.
[chuckles]
Okay.
Once upon a time
there was a beautiful
little princess
who went to
Meadow Crest pre-school
for the very first time.
And can you guess the name
of the beautiful
little princess?
Miss Pinky.
No.
Princess Michelle.
And when Princess Michelle
opened the door, she saw..
...a magic land of fun.
It was like
Disneyland with a nap.
Princess Michelle
made lots of new friends
and they all played
with their toys and then..
What? Oh! Uh,
uh, and then, uh..
And then, they played
with their toys some more.
And then..
...and then they all
cleaned up the mess they made.
And then,
Princess Michelle said
"My first day at pre-school
"was the most wonderful
day of my life."
Awesome!
Okay, miss one-night-away
from pre-school.
Into bed.
Goodnight.
Goodnight, munchkin.
I can't sleep.
This is nuts!
[instrumental music]
Five, six, seven
Eight, nine, 36..
...a hundred.
Ready or not, here I come.
Where are they hiding?
I don't know.
I'm not behind this pointed
headed guy in the mushroom.
I know where Danny is.
- Ha! I found you!
- Oh, nuts!
This game is so hard.
I never win!
Ha ha ha.
Where are you?
- Ha ha ha.
- Ah! I see you.
Ha-hiding! Fine job by Jessie.
The princess is coming.
[cheering]
Hi, people.
(together)
Hi, Princess Michelle.
You're the prettiest princess
in all the land.
You got it, dude!
♪ Yay yay the princess is here ♪
♪ We love the princess
her name is Michelle ♪
♪ Yay yay Princess Michelle ♪♪
I like that song. Sing it again.
♪ Yay yay the princess is here ♪
♪ We love the princess
her name is Michelle ♪
♪ Yay yay Princess Michelle ♪♪
Yay, yay, Princess Michelle.
Wow! I love pre-school.
I'm going now.
I need a car!
D.J., D.J.!
How come you're going
to school so early?
Because I am.
What kind of answer is that?
It's the kind of answer you get
when I don't wanna
tell you something.
Are you meeting somebody?
Is it Kevin? Is it Kimmy?
Is it Kathy?
Is it anyone who
starts with a K?
Here's what starts with a K.
Keep your nose
out of my business.
I gotta say it..
...how rude!
Michelle, what are you doing?
Making lunch for pre-school.
Michelle, come here a minute.
Let me take a look at you.
Michelle..
...your dress is on backwards.
Did you dress
yourself this morning?
Yes, I did.
And did you look in the mirror?
And did you think
you looked good?
Yes, I did.
Oh, well, here's
a little fashion tip.
Walk backwards and
maybe no one will notice.
That's easy.
See you later.
Michelle..
Comet, I think our friend
D.J. is up to something.
Just take a little
stroll over to her
secret hiding place.
Take a peek into her diary.
Just for fun.
Aha!
Hey, there's a note on here.
"Dear, Stephanie
"if you read my diary
"this room will be all mine
"because you will be
living in the backyard."
Ooh, there must be something
really juicy in here.
I'll just get the key..
...from under Melvin's derby.
It's gone!
I can't believe she
doesn't trust her own sister.
There's gotta be
a way into this thing.
[grunting]
Comet, I just broke
the lock on D.J.'s diary.
I've gotta fix
this before D.J. gets home.
[knock on door]
Argh!
Hey, Steff, you ready?
- Where are we going?
- Oh, I don't know.
Paris, Rome, school?
School?
Oh, yeah. I go there.
Comet, what are you chewin' on?
Give me that. Give me that.
Give me that right now.
Oh, gosh! Doggy drool.
This is D.J.'s diary.
You better put it back
in her secret hiding place.
I think it's in the pillow
case this week, isn't it?
Right!
Comet, you rascal.
[instrumental music]
Come on, daddy.
Oh, Michelle, here we go!
Another major
milestone in your life.
Your first day of pre-school.
- Come on, daddy.
- Don't worry.
You're gonna have lots of
fun and make new friends.
Come on, daddy.
You know, I'll never forget
my first day at pre-school.
Bye, daddy.
Oh, Michelle, honey,
wait for me.
[rattling]
Hi, Miss Petrie.
Hello, Mr. Tanner.
Michelle, I'd like you to meet
your teacher, Miss Petrie.
Well, hi, there.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
Boys and girls
let's say hi to our
new friend, Michelle.
(together)
Hi, Michelle.
Hi, people.
I'm the king.
Michelle, this is Aaron.
Aaron gets to wear
the sharing crown
because he shared
his toys today.
Want to see Dave?
- Okay, who's Dave?
- The birdie.
Dave is our class pet.
He's right over there.
Go say hello.
[indistinct chatter]
Well, I guess I'll
just hang out here today.
Well, Michelle seems to
be adjusting very quickly.
But if it would make you
feel better, you're welcome
to stay and have juice
and cookies with us.
[laughing]
I'll check with Michelle.
Michelle, honey..
...do you want daddy
to stay here with you today?
Go home. I'm a big girl.
Okay, then, I'm gonna
come and pick you up
as soon as school's over, okay?
- Okay.
Drive safely.
Thanks, honey.
So, uh, what do I do now?
I cleared my whole day for this.
Oh, that's not really
your problem, is it?
We'll see you in
a couple of hours, Mr. Tanner.
- Thanks.
- Hm-mm.
I know.
I can wax the kitchen floor.
[chuckles]
Alright!
Yeah.
Okay, boys and girls
let's meet on the magic
carpet for story time.
Come on.
Alright, everybody.
Hi, Dave, you're
a pretty birdie.
Ready for a story,
boys and girls?
(together)
Yeah.
Come on, it's story time.
Petrie.
Dave flew out the window.
Michelle did it.
Well, it was just an accident.
I'm sure Michelle
didn't mean to do it.
I'm sorry. I'm a bad girl.
A very bad girl.
I'm a very bad girl.
[dramatic music]
Dave, come back. Where are you?
Yo, Dave, if you're
out there, come back.
Give the kid a break, huh?
Guys, you should have seen
Michelle in pre-school today.
None of the kids
would play with her.
She sat in a corner by herself
saying, "I'm a bad girl."
(together)
Dave!
Dave, the bread is yummy.
Guys, we gotta
do something here.
Jessie, come with me.
Joey..
...please pick up this bread.
[imitating seagull calling]
There! That should hold it.
[grunts]
Uh-oh!
They should put
a warning on this glue.
Oh, they did.
Hey, Steff, what's going on?
Oh, nothing. Nothing at all.
Just another day doing
nothing here in my room.
You know, I was thinking, we
never hang out like we used to.
So, you wanna go
to the mall with me?
This is cool! This is rad!
This is..
...a real bad time.
I am bushed!
Hi, girls, I'm taking Michelle
for some ice-cream.
Who wants to come?
I do..
...not.
Thanks, Joey, but
I'm going to the mall.
She's acting very strange.
Even for her.
Steff, what are you
hiding under the pillow?
Nothing. See, nothing at all.
Nothing.
Hey, how'd this get here?
Steff, give me D.J.'s diary.
[sniggering]
[laughs]
You're in big trouble.
Go find Dave. Fly away.
You're no help.
Guess what, Michelle?
Got you a new birdie friend.
That is not Dave.
This is Sammy.
Say hi to Sammy.
Hi, Sammy. Where is Dave?
Michelle, all the kids
are going to love Sammy
when you bring him
to pre-school tomorrow.
I'm not going to pre-school.
Oh, yes, you are, honey.
No way, Jose.
No one likes me.
Oh-ho-ho-ho!
Hold it there, ankle-biter.
Now, we love you
very very much.
And if you don't
wanna go to pre-school
then you don't have to
go to pre-school, okay?
Yay! Thank you.
Alright. There you go!
- No more school.
- Daniel, problem solved.
No.
Problem made worse.
Jessie, Michelle
has to go to pre-school.
How can you send her back to
school? The kids don't like her.
Look, I know you just wanna
protect her from being hurt.
But we can't be by
her side 24 hours a day
just to stop every bad
thing that might happen.
We have to help her
get through this.
Not run away from it.
Look, I know what
the kid's going through.
In kindergarten, I was
the goldfish monitor.
A part of my job was to take the
goldfish home for the weekend.
I learned
a very important lesson.
When taking a goldfish home,
take the bowl with you.
You killed
the kindergarten goldfish?
Hey, back off, man.
I'm still trying to get over it.
To this day
I can't eat sushi.
So, what happened?
Well, my parents made
me go back to school
and all the kids teased me.
They called me fish hater.
Ooh, brutal!
For how long did this go on?
Well...you know
actually, it went
on till show and tell.
Oh, yeah.
Luckily, Barry Fox brought in
his toenail collection
all the kids turned on him.
I suppose you were
right and I was wrong.
Okay, she should
go back to school.
And who better to tell her
than the man that was right.
Congratulations, daddy.
Thanks.
Thanks, Joey, you saved my life.
Now, Steff, when you break
the next thing you're not
supposed to be touching,
be very careful
with this permanent
glue because as you..
...know, this could happen.
Joey, what are you
doing with my diary?
Ouch!
Well, nice seeing you all again.
Uh, Steff, isn't there
something you would like
to say to D.J. about her diary?
Yes. There is.
D.J., Joey did not
steal your diary.
Michelle did.
[clearing throat]
Maybe it was me.
You know how I am with names.
Joey, may I have a word
alone with my nosey sister?
- Sure.
- Joey, don't go!
Steff, I have to go.
I really wish
I hadn't done that.
Sit.
I'm not gonna yell at you.
I'm just gonna talk in a very
firm voice for a very long time.
Now, why are you always
snooping around in my stuff?
I can't help it.
You fascinate me!
Listen, you have
no business to..
I fascinate you?
Of course, you do.
You go to school dances.
You have seven different
teachers in the same day
and you carry a purse.
You're a woman of the world.
True. But I still
need my privacy.
I'll tell you what.
If you really promise
that my diary is off limits
I'll try to tell you more
about my fascinating life.
I promise.
Forgive me.
I guess so.
Besides, I keep my really
hot stories in my journal.
You have a journal?
Where is it?
What does it look like?
Okay, Michelle,
you wait right here.
I'm gonna talk to
the other boys and girls.
You stay with me all day.
I promise. I won't leave
unless you say it's alright.
- Thank you very much.
- You're welcome.
Now, you stay right here
where I can see you.
- Hi, Miss Petrie.
- Oh, hello, Mr. Tanner.
Boys and girls
Michelle's daddy
wants to talk to you.
- They're all ears.
- Thanks.
- Hi, kids.
- Hi.
I'm Danny Tanner.
I have my own talk show,
"Wake Up, San Francisco."
Oh, well, we're on
opposite Sesame Street
so I guess that's why
you're all so impressed.
My sweet little girl Michelle
has brought someone for you
to keep here at the pre-school
because she likes
you all so very much.
Come on in, Michelle.
(together)
Ooh, a birdie!
Now, talk to the boys and girls.
This is Sammy here
and he's a nice birdie.
I give him to the pre-school.
Michelle, that's very generous.
Why don't we thank Michelle
by clapping our hands.
(together)
Thank you, Michelle.
See, honey, all your new friends
are saying thank you very much.
Welcome very much.
Everyone, come say
hi to our new birdie.
Here, Michelle, you can
wear the sharing crown.
Thank you.
Daddy, I'm a princess.
Yes, you are, Michelle.
You are my little princess.
Sweetheart, I'm very proud
of you for being so brave
and coming to pre-school.
Do you want me to
stay here with you?
No, thank you.
They like me now.
I think you're gonna have a real
good time here in pre-school.
I like being a big girl.
Go play with your
new friends now, honey.
You okay?
Yeah. I'll be fine.
But if she's ever
crowned Miss America
I'll be crying like a baby.
[Sammy chirps]
People, don't open that door.
Remember?
[instrumental music]
[theme music]
♪ Ah ah ah ah ♪
♪ Chip-a-dee-ba-ba-dow ♪♪